片名：《無敵浩克》
(HULK GROWLING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(HULK ROARING)
（爆炸震驚校園）
（卡爾沃大學實驗室的神秘事故）
（目擊到綠色怪物）
（現場找回實驗室器材）
（目標逃脫追捕）
（驚現綠色怪獸）
（採購請求：美國陸軍：斯塔克工業批准 註：《鋼鐵俠》主角開的那個軍工企業）
（截獲消息：伊麗莎白·羅斯博士於2006.2.7與班納聯繫）
（搜捕仍在繼續）
（他還在逃往嗎？）
（已經五個月沒有消息）
(HEART BEATING)
(EXHALES)
(DOG BARKING)
已經158天沒有事故發生
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
可以吃了吧？
Is it ready?
《簡明葡英詞典》
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
嗨！打得好啊
Hey! That's a great punch.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
餓了？
餓了
我們開始練呼吸
這裡，感情
恐懼不是好事，所以要控制感情
(IN ENGLISH) Fear no good.So emotion and control.
(PUFFING)
用你的橫膈膜呼吸（位於胸腔與腹部之間）
控制憤怒最好的辦法
就是控制你的身體
控制你的脈搏
呼吸，呼吸(IN ENGLISH) Breathe. Breathe.
(WATCH BEEPING)
呼吸
(INHALING)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
等等
Wait.
(BEEPING SLOWS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(MACHINES WHIRRING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
好了
Okay.
我可以讓它在工作一陣子，不過你得…
I can make it work for a while,but you need...
(BOTH CHATTERING IN PORTUGUESE)
我得蓋間新工廠
好的，好的
(IN ENGLISH) Okay. Okay.
這五個月多虧你了
你這麼聰明，不該來做臨時工
我給你正式工資吧
關掉！關掉！
Shut that off! Turn it off!
讓開！
Watch out!
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
好了！
Okay!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
想和我一起吃午飯嗎？
滾開，美國佬
想打架啊？
太晚了
別讓我…餓
我要是餓了，你不會…
好過的
好像說錯了(IN ENGLISH) That's not right.
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
(CHATTERING IN PORTUGUESE)
噢，多謝(IN ENGLISH) Oh, you.
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
看看，看見沒？我就要能離開這裡了
You see that? See that?My ticket out of here.
加密中，進度：100% 呼叫藍先生
藍，你在嗎？
綠先生！
很高興聽到你的消息，神秘的朋友！
我找到了
終於等到了
很漂亮的小花，是吧？
記住要多用點劑量，祝你好運:)
該死！
Damn it!
又失敗了
:(你用了多少？
全部
看來該見面了
不安全
你都伽瑪中毒了，同樣不安全
別再找花了
把血樣寄給我
否則幫不了你了
藍先生，紐約
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
阿靈頓，弗吉尼亞
這個也許會更有意思點
SPARR: Here's something a bit more interesting.
該病例我們懷疑是伽瑪中毒暈厥在密爾沃基市
It's a possible gamma sickness. Milwaukee.
一名男子喝了瓜拉那飲料（能刺激神經的功能性植物，產於南美）
A man drank one of those guarana sodas.
但他得到的能量有點過頭了
Guess it had a little more kick than he was looking for.
哇
Wow.
- 飲料在哪裡灌裝的？ - 巴西的波多韋德
- Where was it bottled? - Porto Verde, Brazil.
讓我們的探員去飲料廠找一名白人男子
Have our people look for a white man at the bottling plant.
告訴他們不要接觸他！否則他會消失！
Tell them no contact!If he even sees them, he's gone!
佛特·約翰遜，大沼澤地
我盡力了，時間倉促，不過這些都是精英
I got you who I could.Short notice, but they're all quality.
而且還有一個殺手鑭
And I pulled you one ace.
艾米·布朗斯基，生於俄國，在英國長大
Emil Blonsky.Born in Russia, raised in England.
是從皇家海軍借調到海豹突擊隊的
And on loan to SOCOM from the Royal Marines.
我知道你給了我一些得力干將，喬
GENERAL: I know you cashed in some chips for this, Joe.
很高興能幫助你，要就要最好的
Glad I could help. Just make it good.
這是目標和地點，要捉活的
SPARR: This is the target and the location.Snatch and grab, live capture.
你們可以用釘槍和神經抑制彈
You'll have your dart clips and suppression ordnance,
但是實彈只能在支援的時候使用
but live fire is for backup only.
我們在當地有駐點 不過要做得盡可能安靜
We got local out there,but we want it tight and quiet.
他是個戰士嗎？
Is he a fighter?
你的目標是美國政府通緝的
Your target is a fugitive from the US government
竊取軍事機密的逃犯
who stole military secrets.
同時他還害死了兩名科學家
He is also implicated in the deaths of two scientists,
一位軍官，一位愛達荷州傘兵 可能還有兩名加拿大獵人
a military officer, an Idaho state trooper and possibly two Canadian hunters.
所以別管他是不是戰士！
So don't wait to see if he's a fighter!
把他麻醉了提回來
Tranq him and bring him back.
(LAPTOP BLEEPS)
（加密的呼入消息）好消息
血樣初步檢測結果顯示 伽瑪水平已明顯下降
能治好我嗎？
能
不過…我需要更多數據
不是吧
Oh, come on.
暴露程度、伽瑪粒子濃度、細胞飽和度
不可能，數據不在這裡
那在哪裡？
在家
(MACHINES BEEPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON RADIO)
(DOG BARKING)
(WHINING)
(TRACKER BEEPING INCREASES)
探頭
Camera.
(TRACKER BEEPING RAPIDLY)
進去
Here we go.
把那只該死的狗甩掉
Get rid of the damn dog.
上！
Take him!
目標在移動
Target's on the move.
(GUNSHOT)
(DOG WHINING)
(SCREAMS)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
他在哪兒？
Where is he?
(SHUSHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
他在地面
He's on the ground.
- 我們上！ - 上！
- Let's go! - COMMANDO: Go!
快，快！
Move, move!
謝謝
上,上,上！
Go, go, go!
快,快!
Go! Go!
(SHOUTING)
掃清路面！
COMMANDO: Clear everyone out!
別跟丟了！
Do not lose him!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON RADIO)
哦！不！
Oh! No!
(GRUNTS)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(BEEPING INCREASES)
(INHALING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
從後面包圍他！
Get around behind him!
目標經過090戰士的坐標
Target moving past mobile unit 0-9-0.
哦，不是吧
Oh, no.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
玩笑開大了
You got to be kidding me.
(GROANING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(GATE CLANKING)
(METAL CLANKING)
- 他在哪裡？  - 目標鎖定
- GENERAL ON RADIO: Where is he? - Target acquired.
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(BEEPING SLOWS)
美國佬！
MAN: Gringo!
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
上
(WHISPERING) Let's go.
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
不！
No!
不！請別這樣！
BRUCE: Please! No!
別搶電腦！
Not the computer!
給我！不！
Gimme that! No!
現在怎麼不硬了，嗯？
再耍耍那些招數啊
來啊
請別這樣
我…憤怒…
很嚴重
你不好的生氣，美國佬？我很不好的生氣
(IN ENGLISH) You bad angry, G?I very bad angry.
哦不
Oh, no.
你不明白！事情會一發不可收拾！
You don't understand! Something really bad is about to happen here!
是啊，很嚴重
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(MAN LAUGHING)
有人見過這個嗎？
(WHISPERING) Anybody else seeing this?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(HULK ROARING)
(FEEDBACK ON RADIO)
有妖怪，請指示
COMMANDO 1: We've got a bogey of some kind. Please advice.
那就是目標！用各種麻醉劑！
That is the target!Use every tranq you've got!
馬上動手！
Do it now!
(FIRING)
用實彈，用實彈！
Go live! Go live! Go live!
- 快跑！  - 別擋著！
COMMANDO 1: Move! COMMANDO 2: Get out of the way!
不！
No!
(HULK GROWLING)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
它在我們後面！快跑！
COMMANDO 2: It's behind us! Move! Move!
抓住它！
COMMANDO 1: Get him!
開槍！
Shoot!
(HULK GROWLS)
離我遠點
HULK: Leave me alone.
(GROWLING)
(HULK GRUNTING)
不！不！
No! No!
(HULK ROARING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
我知道開槍之前肯定發生了什麼事
I knew something was different before I got the shot off.
他逃跑的時候帶著這個
He had it on him when he bolted.
女朋友？也許她在幫助他？
Is that a girlfriend? She helps him, maybe?
不用考慮她了
She is no longer a factor.
這事早就結束了，他就一個人
We closed that door to him a long time ago.He's alone.
他想一個人呆著不過得查查他有沒有和別人聯繫
He wants to be alone.But see if he's been talking to anybody.
打擾了一下，長官？
Forgive me, sir?
您不想解釋一下當時的情況？因為…
Doesn't anybody want to talk about what went down in there? 'Cause...
我們沒有被他甩掉
He didn't lose us.
他不是一個人，長官，我們盯住他了
And he was not alone, sir. We had him.
然後我們被一個東西攻擊了，一個…
And then something hit us, something...
很龐大的東西！
Something big hit us!
叉車對它來說就像是一個壘球
It threw a forklift truck like it was a softball!
那是我見過的最強大的生物
It was the most powerful thing I've ever seen.
不過，它已經消失了
Well, it's gone.
但要是班納知道那是什麼
Well, if Banner knows what it is,
我一定會抓到他，踩著他的喉嚨
I'm gonna track him down,I'm gonna put my foot on his throat
- 然後…  - 那就是班納
- and I'm gonna... - That was Banner.
它
It
就是班納
was Banner.
- 您得跟我說清楚，長官  - 算了吧
- You have to explain that statement, sir. - No, I don't.
你幹的很漂亮
You've done a good job.
讓大家收拾收拾上飛機，我們要回去了
Pack up and get our men on a plane.We're going home.
已經1天沒有事故
停車
Wait.
拜託
Please.
能幫我嗎？
我不會說葡萄牙語
我這是在哪兒？（英語）
(IN ENGLISH) Where am I?
我這是在哪兒？（西班牙語）
危地馬拉
我要去前面的鎮子
能幫我嗎？
進來
來，披上這個
你要去哪兒？
回家
我也曾在狗屎任務裡陷入絕境
BLONSKY: I've run into bad situations on crap missions before.
我也見過優秀的戰士
I've seen good men go down
因為對任務不瞭解，而白白送命
purely because someone didn't let us know what we were walking into.
但我總是迎接下一個任務，從不回頭因為這就是我的職責，對吧？
I've moved on to the next one,because that's what we do, right?
這就是我的使命
I mean, that's the job.
但這次？
But this?
這次可不是一般的詭異
This is a whole new level of weird.
我完全不想就這麼抽身離去
And I don't feel inclined to step away from it.
所以如果您還想再次行動，算我一個
So if you're taking another crack at him,I want in.
還有，恕我直言，下一次您應該讓大家做好充分的準備
And, with respect, you should be looking for a team that's prepped and ready to fight,
否則的話，如果那怪物再出現
because if that thing shows up again,
您請來的精英們大多都會嚇得尿褲子
you're gonna have a lot of professional tough guys pissing in their pants.
長官
Sir.
(HENS CLUCKING)
(DOG BARKING)
恰帕斯，墨西哥
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(COINS CLINKING)
(CHATTERING IN SPANISH)
有更有彈性的嗎？
Tienes mas stretchy?
嗯，很好
Yeah. Perfecto.
(MOTORCYCLE PASSING)
我再重申一次
Let me emphasise that what I'm about to share with you
這事對於我和軍隊來說，都是高度機密的
is tremendously sensitive,both to me personally and the Army.
你應該知道我們有一個步兵武器研發計劃
You're aware that we've got an Infantry Weapons Development programme.
在二戰期間，軍方啟動了一個子計劃
Well, in WWll, they initiated a subprogram
用於增強生化科技戰鬥力
for Bio-Tech Force Enhancement.
嗯，超級士兵
Yeah, Super Soldier.
對
Yes.
簡單來說，就是這個意思
An oversimplification, but yes.
現在，我又重新開始推動這個計劃做一些認真的，勇敢的嘗試
And I dusted it off, got 'em doing serious work again, bold work.
他們想做的是把你武裝的更強大
Across the hall,they were trying to arm you better.
而我們想做的，是讓你變得更強大
We were tryin' to make you better.
那時班納的工作還處於起步階段還談不上什麼武器
Banner's work was very early phase.It wasn't even weapons application.
他以為自己在做抗輻射試驗
He thought he was working on radiation resistance.
我可不會告訴他這個計劃的真實情況
I would never have told him what the project really was.
但他過於自信，以至於要拿自己做試驗
But he was so sure of what he was onto,that he tested it on himself.
而試驗出了很大的問題
And something went very wrong.
不過也可以說是無心插柳
Or it went very right.
對我而言，那小子的身體就是屬於美國陸軍的
As far as I'm concerned, that man's whole body is the property of the US Army.
您剛才說他不是在做武器試驗？
You said he wasn't working on weapons, right?
- 對  - 但您是這麼計劃的，是吧？
- No. - But you were. You were, weren't you?
您另有打算
You were trying other things.
我們研製的一種血清
One serum we developed
很有前景
was very promising.
- 但他為什麼跑了？ - 他是個科學家
- So why did he run? - He's a scientist.
跟我們不一樣
He is not one of us.
- 布朗斯基，你幾歲了？45？  - 39
- Blonsky, how old are you? 45? - 39.
- 有點力不從心了吧？  - 沒錯
- It takes a toll, doesn't it? - Yes, it does.
那就別再戰鬥了
So get out of the trenches.
從你的檔案看，你現在都該是上校了
You should be a Colonel by now,with your record.
不，我是個戰士，我會戰鬥到最後一刻
No, I'm a fighter.I'll be one for as long as I can.
知道麼，以我現在的見識加上我十年前的身體
You know, if I could take what I know now,put it in the body I had ten years ago,
那會是一個讓現在的我都恐懼的對手
that would be someone I wouldn't want to fight.
也許我可以給你這樣的機會
I could probably arrange something like that.
卡爾沃大學，弗吉尼亞
已經17天沒有事故
伊麗莎白·羅斯博士，分子生物學
斯坦利的比薩屋
路上小心，孩子們
Take care, kids.
斯坦，我向你保證
Stan, I give you my word,
你聽到的任何關於我的消息，都是假的
whatever you've heard about me,it's not true.
我知道，我一直都知道
Oh, I know it. I always knew it.
你知道我對你們倆的感情
I mean, you know how I felt about you two.
- 你和她見面了嗎？  - 沒
- Have you talked to her? - No.
她不知道我在這裡了
She doesn't know that I'm here.
- 她有男朋友嗎？  - 嗯，一個心理學家
- She's with somebody? - Yeah, he's a head shrink.
據說學術上很有成就。他的確是個好小伙子
They say he's one of the best.But a really nice guy.
好，很好
Good. That's good.
- 我能幫你什麼嗎，布魯斯？  - 方便的話我想有張床睡幾天
- Bruce, what can I do to help you? - I could use a bed for a few nights.
- 樓上有空的房間  - 那太好了
- You can have the spare room upstairs. - That'd be so great.
還有另一件事
There is one other thing.
抱歉，借過
Excuse me. Pardon me.
借過
Coming through.
嘿，哥們，五樓有叫外賣的
Hey, pal. I got a delivery on five.
那上面沒人
I don't think there's anybody up there.
噢，我要是沒收到錢會很慘的,請讓我上去看看吧
Oh, man. I'm gonna catch hell if I don't collect. You got to let me try.
對了，我多出一塊中號的，拿著吧
I'll tell you what. I got an extra medium.Take it on the house.
- 真是找對人了  - 上帝保佑你，兄弟
- You are the man. - God bless you, brother.
太好了
All right.
(COMPUTERS BLEEPING)
伊麗莎白·羅斯博士
密碼：
行了
Okay.
（伽瑪脈衝）
（沒有結果）
（B·班納）
呼叫藍先生
綠先生！搜索結果如何？
數據沒了
這樣…
我就無能為力了
現在準備怎樣？
還得繼續逃命
要關門了，各位，不好意思
We're pretty well closed here, folks.I'm sorry.
噢，拜託，斯坦，這可是週五晚上呢
Oh, come on, Stan. It's Friday night.
是你們啊
Oh, kids.
現在只有海員沙司（意大利菜）了
I got nothing but marinara now.
哦，我一定得來一塊紅粉比薩
Oh, I got to have a Mister Pink, please.
她又工作得錯過晚飯了
She worked through dinner again,of course.
斯坦？
Stan?
然後我說，「我的意思是，你在哪裡？」
And he... I go, " So, yeah,I mean, where were you?
「我都不知道你在哪裡，塞西爾」
"I can't... I don't know where you were, Cecil."
他說，「反正不和你在一起」
And he goes, "Not where you been at."
「噢，天吶」，我感覺糟透了
I thought, "Oh, my God." I just felt so awful.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
布魯斯？
Bruce?
貝蒂？怎麼了？
Betty? What's going on?
貝蒂…
Betty...
告訴我，我看到的是不是真的
Just tell me if I saw what I think I saw.
- 我不知道該怎麼跟你說  - 請告訴我真相
- I don't know what to say. - Please, just tell me the truth.
別離開我，別離開我
BETTY: Don't go. Don't go.
我要你跟我回去
I want you to come with me now.
求你了，跟我回去
Please. Come with me.
求你了
Please.
這就是我們的數據
BETTY: It's our data.
我在他們搬東西之前進去拿到的
I got in there before they carted it all away.
我希望哪一天能派上用場
I hoped somewhere that it might tell us something someday.
- 將軍知道你拿著這個嗎？  - 我想他不知道
- Does the General know that you have this? - No, I don't think so.
我幾年沒和他說話了
I haven't spoken to him in a couple of years.
你要確定
You have to be sure.
布魯斯，我就是不明白,為什麼我們不能一起去和他談談
Bruce, I don't understand why we can't just go in there together and talk to him.
他告訴了我他的意圖,他想從我這裡拿到他想要的東西
He told me what he wanted to do.He wants it out of me.
他想研究我的身體，這樣他就能夠複製
He wants to dissect it so that he can replicate it.
他想把我變成武器
He wants to make it a weapon.
（斯塔克工業）
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 我想你也許需要…  - 謝謝
- I thought you might want to... - Thanks.
我該走了，越早越好
Listen, I should leave early,as early as I can.
真的？就不能留下來？
Really? You can't stay at all?
我也想，但這裡不安全
I want to,but it's just not safe for me to be here.
- 如果能借點錢…  - 沒問題
- If I could borrow some cash... - Of course.
我要坐公車
I need to take a bus.
那就讓我送你去車站
Well, at least let me walk you to the station.
好
Okay.
- 東西都帶齊了？  - 嗯
- You have everything you need? - Yeah.
我…
I...
怎麼？
What?
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
希望你能休息好
I hope you get some rest.
我們只給你很小的劑量
We're giving you a very low dose only.
你要警惕，要遵守紀律
I need you sharp out there and disciplined.
一旦有副作用的感覺
First sign of any side effect,
00:46:45,9，25 --> 00:46:49,595
我們就停止,你要等到恢復以後再做下次試驗
we stop and you're off team until you straighten out.
- 同意嗎  - 同意
- Agreed? - Agreed.
我們會有兩條注射管
You'll get two separate infusions.
一條注射到肌肉深處,一條注射到脊椎中央
One into the deep muscle,one into the bone marrow centres.
注射到脊髓可能會痛
The bone ones are going to hurt.
(GRUNTS)
沒事吧？
Is everything okay?
還好
I think so.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
過來
Come here.
- 我就是想幫你  - 哦
- I just wanna do this. - Oh.
- 這樣更好  - 是嗎？
- It's better like that. - Yeah?
太小了一點吧？
It feels too tight, huh?
- 是有點  - 嗯
- Yeah, a little. - Okay.
- 怎麼？  - 他們來了
- What? - They're here.
- 貝蒂，看著我，看著我！  - 布魯斯！
- Betty, look at me, look at me! - Bruce!
遠離我，越遠越好！
You have to go far away from me as you can!
- 別問我為什麼，走，快走！  - 布魯斯！
- Don't argue with me, just go. Go! - Bruce!
(CAR ALARM SOUNDING)
該死！再有三分鐘，狙擊手就能到位了
Damn it! We'd have had snipers on target in three more minutes.
誰這麼毛手毛腳的！
I wanna know who jumped the gun.
他朝270方向去了
He's heading 2-7-0.
布朗斯基！先別！
Blonsky! Not yet!
長官
Sir.
小心點，會很有意思的
Look alive. This could get interesting.
他在這裡！
I got him!
停下！停下！
Stop! Stop!
我知道你在裡面！
I know you're in there!
求你了，將軍！
General, please!
長官？
Sir?
爸爸！
Dad!
- 爸，請別這樣  - 你不明白，給我進去
- Dad, please don't do this. - You can't see this clearly. Now, get inside.
他在那裡！
There he is!
目標在天橋，我們看見了
SOLDIER 1 ON RADIO,Target is in the overpass. We have a visual.
不要交火！重複，不要交火！
Do not engage! Repeat, do not engage!
他被困住了
SOLDIER 2: He's locked in.
扔兩個催淚彈進去
Put two canisters in there with him.
開火！
SOLDIER: Fire!
抓她回來！
Get her back here!
(GRUNTING)
現在她要看到了
Now she'll see.
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
A隊何在？
Alpha team?
讓他享受炮火吧
Let him have all of it.
朝他開火！
SOLDIER 2: Come on, light him up!
越野戰車在哪裡？趕緊過來！
Where are the fifty cals? Move your asses!
(GRUNTING)
哦，天！
Oh, my God!
布朗斯基，該你了！
Blonsky, now you're up!
長官？
Sir?
掩護我
Cover me.
(GROWLING)
還記得我嗎？
Remember me?
天，不錯啊
My God, he's doing it.
把他往加農炮方向引！
Move him toward the cannons!
快！
SOLDIER: Move!
(GROWLS)
原地待命！
Hold your position!
可以了！
BLONSKY: Do it now!
(HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING)
(GRUNTING)
求你了，求你了，不要！
Please, please, please, no!
- 求你了，求你了！   - 拉開她！
- Please, please, please! - Get her back!
你會殺了他的！
You're killing him!
住手！放開我！
BETTY: Stop! Get off of me!
布魯斯！
(DISTORTED) Bruce!
布魯斯！布魯斯！
Bruce! Bruce!
武裝直升機呢？
Where's the gunship?
就這樣了？
Is that it?
布朗斯基，回撤！
Blonsky, pull back now.
回撤！
Pull back!
你就這麼兩下子？
Is that all you got?
(GROWLS)
- 退後！ - 退後！快，快！
-Fall back! -SOLDIER 3: Fall back! Let's go, let's go!
找掩護！
GENERAL: Find cover!
貝蒂！
Betty!
開火，該死！
Fire, goddamn it!
布魯斯？
Bruce?
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
停火！
Stop firing!
不！
No!
(GROWLS)
你打電話給我們是對的
You did the right thing, calling us.
我想知道他們去哪裡了
I need to know where they're going.
只要和他在一起，她的處境就極度危險
She'll be in incredible danger as long as she's with him.
哪來的危險？
From who?
他保護了她，而你差點殺了她
He protected her. You almost killed her.
我向你保證 我現在考慮最多的就是她的安全
I give you my word, her safety is my main concern at this point.
知道嗎，幹這行最讓我自豪的
You know, it's a point of professional pride with me
就是能分辨出別人是否在撒謊
that I can always tell when somebody's lying.
你就是在撒謊
And you are.
我不知道他去哪裡了
I don't know where he's going.
- 我知道她會盡力幫他的  - 那她就是從犯了
-I know she'll help him, if she can. -Then she's aiding a fugitive.
那樣我可幫不了他們了
And I can't help either one of them.
我以前不明白為什麼她從不提起你
I used to wonder why she never talked about you.
現在我知道了！
Now I know!
她都是在哪裡認識這些人的？
GENERAL: Where does she meet these guys?
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
布魯斯？
Bruce?
布魯斯
Bruce.
(ROARING)
沒事了，沒事了
It's okay. It's okay.
過來，來這裡
Come here. Come this way.
小心頭
Watch your head.
好了
Okay.
我們安全了
We're okay.
沒事了
It's okay.
下雨而已
It's just the rain.
他還能再走路嗎？
GENERAL: Will he ever walk again?
看起來他大部分骨頭都已經粉碎了
DOCTOR: Most of the bones in his body look like crushed gravel right now.
不過他的心臟堅強的跟機器一樣
I will say this for him.He's got a heart like a machine.
除了賽馬之外，我還從沒見過這樣的
Never seen anything like it,outside of a racehorse.
過來
Here.
到了
Okay.
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(BRUCE VOMlTING)
布魯斯？
Bruce?
嗨
Oh, hi.
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
其實呢，已經好很多了
Yeah, actually, I feel a lot better.
- 很好  - 我只是得把數據拿回來
-Good. -I just had to get my data back.
你吞下去了？
You ate it?
嗯，那種情況下必須急中生智
Well, you know, the circumstances called for a little improvisation.
哇
Wow.
我沒找到太好的，不過還是買了一些
Okay, so they didn't have a great selection,but I got you some options.
首先
First thing's first.
開玩笑吧
Oh, you're kidding me.
怎麼？
What?
- 不行  - 這是他們那裡最有彈性的了
-No. -They were the stretchiest pair they had.
那我只好試試看了
I'll take my chances.
關於美軍和不明生物
FEMALE REPORTER.; Rumours continue to swirl about a violent clash
今天早些時候在卡爾沃大學交火的傳言
between forces of the US military and an unknown adversary
已經愈演愈烈
on the campus of Culver University earlier today.
二年級學生傑克·麥吉爾和吉姆·威爾遜,目擊了部分戰鬥場面
Sophomores Jack McGhee and Jim Wilson witnessed some of the battle.
真的很大
JIM.; It was so big.
- 就像是浩克一樣！  - 對
-It was like this huge, like, hulk! -Yeah.
麥吉爾正好是校報的記者
FEMALE REPORTER.; McGhee, who happens to be a reporter for the campus paper,
他用手機拍下了畫面
captured this on his cell phone.
關於這個神秘「浩克」的搜尋工作
Further search for the mysterious ''hulk''
由於煙山國家森林公園的暴風雨而推遲
was postponed by powerful thunderstorms in the Smoky Mountain National Forest.
後面別太短
Not too short back there.
我以前也是幫你剪過的，記得麼
I have done this before, you know.
不知道這麼些年你一個人是怎麼過來的
I don't know how you've done this on your own for all this time.
一般是用大剪刀
With clippers, usually.
(BETTY CHUCKLING)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
- 等等，等等 - 怎麼？
-Wait, wait, wait. Wait. -What? What?
還是別做了
We can't do this.
- 沒事的，我想要  - 不行
-It's okay. I want to. -No.
不
No.
不行
I can't .
(BEEPING SLOWS)
我不能太興奮
I can't get too excited.
(BEEPING STOPS)
一點點也不行？
Not even a little excited?
(BRUCE SlGHS)
好吧
BETTY: It's okay.
先生，是布朗斯基的事
Sir, it's Blonsky.
能聯繫到他的家屬嗎？
Has anyone found out if he has next of kin or family?
您自己問他吧
Ask him yourself.
長官？
Sir?
- 看到你恢復很高興，戰士  - 謝謝，長官
-Good to see you back on your feet, soldier. -Thank you, sir.
感覺如何？
How do you feel?
很生氣，準備第三波戰鬥
Pissed off and ready for round three.
基本上這些都不能帶  因為他們都能跟蹤到
Basically, we can't use any of this,because they can track all of it.
唇膏呢？也能跟蹤到？
Well, my lip gloss? Can they track that?
- 不會，你可以帶著  - 謝謝
-No. You can take your lip gloss. -Thank you.
- 我還要眼鏡  - 行，也可以帶著
-Well, I need my glasses. -Well, you can take
- 眼鏡和手錶，好嗎？ - 嗯
-your glasses and your watch, okay? -Okay.
除了信用卡，身份證和手機 其他都能帶
We can use most of it. We just can't use the credit cards, the ID or the phone.
- 手機別開機 - 好
-Don't even turn that on. -Okay.
還要帶現金
And we'll take the cash, obviously.
只帶四十塊錢，又沒有信用卡 能去哪裡？
How will we get where we need to go on $40 and no credit cards?
那，可以賣掉這個
Well, we could sell this.
不行，這是你母親留給你的唯一的東西了
No. No, that's the only thing you have left from her. No.
那我們得試著再贖回來了
Well, we'll have to try and get it back.
聯邦調查局已經在監控通話
SPARR: Federal is already monitoring phones,
信用卡，以及羅斯博士的網絡賬號
plastic and Dr Ross's web accounts,
當地警局也已處於警備狀態
and local PD have been placed on alert.
一旦他們出現，消息會直接傳到我們這裡
They'll pop up somewhere and when they do, it comes straight to us.
他們不會突然出現的
GENERAL: They're not gonna just pop up.
他花了五年時間 神不知鬼不覺的越過了邊境
He made it five years and got across borders without making any mistakes.
他現在可不會用什麼信用卡
He's not gonna use a damn credit card now.
他要是想逃，那早走了
If he was trying to escape, he'd be long gone.
現在他不是想逃走
He's not trying to escape this time.
他正在尋求幫助，這才是我們的線索
He's looking for help and that's how we're gonna get him.
我們知道他們要的是什麼 我們也知道他一直在和人聯繫
We know what they're after and we know he's been talking to somebody.
你們都有通信的備份
You all have copies of the correspondence.
綠先生和藍先生的聯絡
The aliases Mr Green and Mr Blue
已經納入了神盾數據庫的監控
have been added to the SHIELD Operations Database.
我們只要守株待兔，等他們再聯繫
If he comes up for air, we'll be waiting.
（藍先生，附上數據，是時候見面了綠先生）
只要他有動靜，我們就能知道
If he makes a peep, we'll hear him.
而他冒出來的時候，我們將會等著他
And when he slips up, we'll be ready.
（國土戰略干預組·後勤部）
（藍先生，附上數據，是時候見面了綠先生）
（格雷本學院）
（細胞生命系）
（塞繆爾·史登博士）
（匹配數據）
（塞繆爾·史登博士，紐約市）
嘿
Hey.
笑一個
Smile.
那是什麼樣的感覺？
What is it like?
變身的時候，什麼感覺？
When it happens, what do you experience?
記得我們在哈佛的時候 自願參加的那些試驗嗎？
Remember those experiments we volunteered for at Harvard?
誘發幻覺試驗？
Those induced hallucinations?
很像那個，只不過放大了一千倍
It's a lot like that,just a thousand times amplified.
我的腦子裡就像被倒入了一升的酸
It's like someone's poured a litre of acid into my brain.
- 還記得什麼嗎？  - 一些碎片，圖像
-Do you remember anything? -Just fragments. Images.
干擾太多，實在記不起什麼了
There's too much noise.I can never derive anything out of it.
- 但那終歸是你  - 不，不是了
-But then it's still you inside it. -No. No, it's not.
我不知道，在洞穴的時候 我真的感覺它認識我
I don't know.In the cave, I really felt like it knew me.
也許你的心還在那裡
Maybe your mind is in there,
只是過載了，無法正常處理形勢了
it's just overcharged and can't process what's happening.
我不想控制它，我想擺脫它
I don't want to control it.I want to get rid of it.
準備好了嗎？
Are you ready?
讓我們把戰鬥變得更公平些
Let's even the playing field a little.
先生們
Gentlemen.
(HORN BLARING)
布魯斯，醒醒，有狀況
BETTY: Bruce, wake up.There's something going on.
（請準備停車）
（前方檢查）
我們得走了，慢慢往後，別太快
We got to go. Walk toward the back.Just don't move too fast.
好了，來
All right. Come.
到郊區還很遠，坐地鐵會比較快
BETTY: It is a long way uptown.I think the subway's probably quickest.
你讓我在世上最擁擠的城市和數百人一起
Me in a metal tube, deep underground,
擠在地下的鐵罐子裡？
with hundreds of people in the most aggressive city in the world?
好吧，打車
Right. Let's get a cab.
上路啦！你們開得這麼慢，跟娘們似的！
CAB DRlVER: Come on, now! Let's go!You're too slow! You drive like a woman!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
- 真漂亮，看到她的表情沒？  - 噢天
-Very nice. You see her? -Oh, my.
很好，小心，白癡！
Very pretty. Watch out, you goat!
呼吸，呼吸
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
你瘋了嗎？
Are you out of your mind?
- 你怎麼了？  - 怎麼了，寶貝？
-What is wrong with you? -What's the matter, baby?
不喜歡我的風格？
You don't like a good ride?
(GRUNTING)
混蛋！
Asshole!
(BETTY GRUNTS)
我知道一些技巧，可以幫你有效的
You know, I know a few techniques could help you
- 控制怒氣  - 閉嘴，走路
-manage that anger very effectively. -You zip it. We're walking.
好吧
Okay.
打擾了，史登博士？
Excuse me. Dr Sterns?
- 是我  - 不好意思打擾了，我是伊麗莎白·羅斯
-Yes. -I'm sorry to bother you. I'm Elizabeth Ross.
哦！羅斯博士！
Oh! Dr Ross!
- 我想為您引見一個人  - 好
-I have someone who'd like to meet you. -Okay.
藍先生，是你嗎？
It's Mr Blue, isn't it?
綠先生？
Mr Green?
告訴你，我曾經都懷疑你的存在
I got to tell you,I've been wondering if you were even real.
我想如果你不是虛擬的，那會是什麼樣？
And if you were, what would it look like?
身上潛伏著那麼巨大的能量
A person with that much power lurking in him.
想不到真的能在現實中和你握手
Nothing could have surprised me more
這真是太讓人太驚喜了
than this unassuming man shaking my hand.
不過我們可不是要過家家
But, look. We're not strolling into the park for a picnic, here.
即使一切順利
Even if everything goes perfectly,
即使我們能讓你變身，而且控制好劑量
if we induce an episode,if we get the dosage exactly right,
但那會是持久有效的治癒
is that going to be a lasting cure
還是只是暫時的抑制呢？
or just some antidote to suppress that specific flare-up?
不得而知了
I don't know.
我的意思是，即使多出這麼一點點劑量
What I'm saying is that if we overshoot this by even the smallest integer
那裡面濃縮的也是多得驚人的毒素
we're dealing with concentrations with extraordinary levels of toxicity.
- 你是說會害死他  - 害死他？對，是這個意思
-You mean it could kill him. -Kill him? Yeah. I should say so.
還有另一種情況
You should know that there's a flip side to this, too.
如果劑量少了 如果我變身了而治療又失敗了
If we miss on the low side,if we induce me and it fails,
那你可就危險了
this will be very dangerous for you.
聽著，我行事一向以好奇心驅使多過謹慎
Look. I've always been more curious than cautious,
不過到目前為止還沒出過什麼事 那我們到底做不做試驗？
and that's served me pretty well.So, are we going to do this?
感覺如何，夥計？
How you feeling, man?
像野獸一樣
Like a monster.
好吧，上桌子
Okay. On the table.
如果反應劇烈，這些能就你
These will protect you from yourself if you have a strong reaction.
你可以事後再告訴我反應是否劇烈
You can tell me later if you thought it was strong.
噢，不是吧！那幫白癡研究生
Oh, come on! Stupid graduate students.
好的…
Okay...
這個，這個，還有這個
You, you, you.
這將會是從未有過的奇妙體驗
This will be a somewhat novel sensation.
(MACHINE STARTING UP)
開始了
We have begun.
透析機會把解毒藥和你的血液混合
The dialysis machine will mix the antidote with your blood.
只不過解毒藥要等到完全反應時 才能加入
Except the antidote will only take hold once we've achieved a full reaction.
放鬆吧
Just relax.
好了，進入狀態了
Okay. We are comprehensive.
這個給你
Here you go.
好了，準備好了嗎？
All right. We set to pop?
換我就不會抓他手
I'd take your hands off him.
(GRUNTING)
噢天！
Oh, my God!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
等等！還有！等等！
Wait, wait! There's more! Wait!
- 現在可以了，快！  - 等等
-Now. Okay, now! -STERNS: Wait.
趕緊！快點！
Now, do it! Do it!
布魯斯！布魯斯，看著我
Bruce! Bruce, look at me.
挺住，趕緊加解毒藥！史登，快點！
Stay with me. The antidote, now!Sterns, do it now!
布魯斯，看著我，看著我的眼睛 求你了，看著我的眼睛
Bruce, look at me. Look in my eyes.Please, look in my eyes.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
開玩笑吧！
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
(HULK GROANING)
布魯斯
Bruce.
噢天
Oh, my God.
布魯斯？布魯斯，能聽到我說話嗎？
Bruce? Bruce, can you hear me?
布魯斯？
Bruce?
(GASPS)
沒事了，沒事了
It's okay. You're okay. You're okay.
你挺過來了
You did it.
他沒事了，太奇妙了
He's fine. This is fantastic.
結束了
BETTY: It's over.
嗨
Hi.
這是我這輩子見過的最不可思議的情景！
That was the most extraordinary thing I have seen in my entire life!
你消停一下吧，求你了
Okay, you know what? Stop, please.
我們得談談剛才發生的事
We need to go back and talk about what just happened in there.
顯然伽瑪脈衝來自扁桃腺
Absolutely. Okay. The gamma pulse came from the amygdala.
- 我想羅斯博士的核酸合成引物… - 你還好吧？
-I think Dr Ross's primer... -Are you okay?
使得細胞暫時吸收了能量，然後又減弱
...lets the cells absorb the energy temporarily, and then it abates.
這就是你數年前沒有死於輻射的原因！
That's why you didn't die of radiation sickness years ago!
現在，也許我們已經永久的 幹掉這些細胞了
Now, maybe we've neutralised those cells permanently,
但也許只是暫時抑制住了
or maybe we just suppressed that event.
我傾向於後者，但目前還不好說
I'm inclined to think the latter,but it's hard to know
因為我們的試驗樣本都沒有生還
because none of our test subjects ever survived.
- 當然了，因為它們沒有核酸合成引物… - 等等
-Of course, they weren't getting the primer! -Wait, wait.
- 等等，你剛才說什麼？ - 他們沒有
-Wait, what did you just say? -They weren't getting
- 肌肉抑制素核酸合成引物 - 不是，試驗樣本？
-the myostatin primer... -No, no, no. Test subjects?
什麼試驗樣本？
What test subjects?
跟我來
Come with me.
- 情況如何？ - 狙擊手已經能覆蓋A區了
-SPARR: What's the activity level? -Snipers are covering Alpha sector.
我們從小白鼠下手
STERNS ON RADIO.;We started on rats and mice,
不過試驗一開始它們就被烤焦了 所以我們得找大點的動物
but it just compIeteIy fried them,so we had to go bigger.
我們還不清楚，伽瑪和你的血液 哪個更具毒性
And we still don't know which is more toxic,the gamma or your blood.
- 我的血液？什麼意思？ - 布魯斯，這些都是你的
-What do you mean, my blood? -Bruce, this is all you.
你沒給我寄太多，所以我只好通過濃縮 製造更多樣本
You didn't send me much to work with,so I had to concentrate it and make more.
通過試錯法，這個試驗將潛力無窮
With a little more trial and error,there's no end to what we can do!
多麼偉大的工程！
This is potentially Olympian!
伽瑪技術的應用前景很廣
This gamma technology has limitless applications.
數百種治病方法將誕生
We'll unlock hundreds of cures.
人類從此將免受疾病困擾！
We will make humans impervious to disease!
不行，我們得毀了它們
No, no, we've got to destroy it.
- 等等，什麼？ - 全部
-Wait, what? -All of it.
今晚我們就得把它們都毀了
Tonight. We're gonna incinerate it.
- 這是總開關？ - 等等…
-Is this the whole supply? -What...
我們可以因此得到諾貝爾！
We could get the Nobel for this!
你不明白這東西的威力
You don't understand the power of this thing.
這太危險了，我們無法控制
It is too dangerous. It cannot be controlled.
狙擊手，自行掌握開槍時機
At your discretion, shooter.
…我們三個！這是普羅米修斯之火啊（意為將開創生物學新時代）
STERNS ON RADIO.; ...three of us!This is Promethean fire!
但是…
BRUCE ON RADIO.; It's just...
無法瞄準
SOLDIER ON RADIO.; No shot.
布朗斯基進去了
Blonsky's going in.
布朗斯基，別衝動，我女兒在裡面！
GENERAL.; Blonsky, stand down.My daughter's in there!
我們已經有解毒藥了
We have the antidote now.
他們要的不是解毒藥！他們想製造武器！
They don't want the antidote!They want to make it a weapon!
(SIRENS WAlLING)
這事會變得一發不可收拾
And if we let it go, we will never get it back.
你不知道這東西的威力
You don't know how powerful this thing is.
我和別人一樣痛恨政府
I hate the government just as much as anyone,
但你不覺得自己有點偏執了？
but you're being a little paranoid,don't you think?
(GASPS)
布魯斯！布魯斯！
Bruce! Bruce!
出去
Get out.
(BETTY SCREAMS)
它在哪裡？快點，它在哪裡？
Where is it? Come on, where is it?
(BRUCE EXCLAIMS)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
讓它出現吧
Show him to me.
布朗斯基！
Blonsky!
(HEART BEATING SLOWLY)
小姐！
SOLDIER: Miss!
披著這個
Take this.
你相信不相信 我要你這輩子生不如死
If you took it from me, I'm gonna put you in a hole for the rest of your life.
貝蒂
Betty.
我這輩子都不會原諒你對他的所作所為
I will never forgive what you've done to him.
你為了掩蓋你的失敗，保住你的烏紗
He's a fugitive.
才讓他成了逃犯
You made him a fugitive
而讓他變成逃犯的
to cover your failures and to protect your career.
別再當我是你女兒了
Don't ever speak to me as your daughter again.
你要不是我女兒，現在也已經被銬上了
It's only because you're my daughter that you're not in handcuffs, too.
你是說你還能造出更多那樣的怪獸？
SPARR: Are you telling me you can make more like him?
不！還沒，我只是明白了一點點,但還遠不清楚具體細節
No! Not yet. I sorted out a few pieces,but it's not like I can put together
你說的那種矮胖子，我怎麼可能造得出來
the same Humpty Dumpty,if that's what you're asking.
他是詭異的意外的產物 我們能做的只是讓它更強
He was a freak accident!The goal is to do it better!
那麼只有班納一個…
So Banner's the only...
- 這婊子真囉嗦  - 你為什麼老是打人？
-She's an annoying bitch. -Why are you always hitting people?
憑什麼你又這樣對我？
Now what possibly could I have done to deserve such aggression?
不是你做了什麼，而是我要你做什麼
It's not what you've done.It's what you're gonna do.
我要你把我變成班納那樣
I want what you got out of Banner.I want that.
看樣子你體內已經有了點什麼，是吧？
You look like you've got a little something in you already, don't you?
還不夠，你見過他變身的樣子吧？
I want more.You've seen what he becomes, right?
是的
I have.
太美妙了
And it's beautiful.
神仙一樣
Godlike.
那好，我要的就是那個
Well, I want that.
我需要變成那樣，讓我變成那樣
I need that. Make me that.
我不知道你體內已經有了什麼
I don't know what you've got inside you already.
搞不好可能變成
The mix could be
憎惡
an abomination.
我沒說我不願意
(GASPlNG) I didn't say I was unwilling.
我只是想讓你充分知情而已
I just need informed consent.
現在不就行了麼
And you've given it.
（綠先生，強度：14.36%）
我想要和你解釋的就是這個
This is what I was trying to explain.
我不知道你把你自己怎麼了
I don't know what you've been ladling into yourself.
不過顯然起作用了
But clearly it worked.
假設你聽不懂我說的話
Let's assume you don't understand a word I'm saying,
但如果你回到桌子上
but if you'll just get back on the table,
我能把你治好
I can fix this.
(ABOMINATION GROWLING)
(ABOMINATION LAUGHlNG)
- 開槍！  - 嗨！
SOLDIER 1 : Shoot it! SOLDIER 2: Hey!
不！
No!
(SOLDIERS SCREAMlNG)
D4小隊報告
SOLDIER 5: Delta 4 to Leader.
他們幹掉了我們兩個人，兩個人！
They took out two of our guys,two of our guys!
布朗斯基和少校還在裡面！
Blonsky and the Major are still inside!
(ABOMINATION GROWLING)
快點！快，快，快！
Come on! Move, move, move, move!
就在那裡！
It's over there!
放開他們！
SOLDIER 2: Drop them!
- 那是什麼？  - 開火！
SOLDIER 3: What is that thing? SOLDIER 4: Shoot it!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
好吧！你…你來開車！我們走！走！
Okay. All right! You... You, drive!Let's go! Move, move!
- D4小隊報告！ - 行動！行動！
SOLDIER 5: Delta 4 to Leader!SOLDIER 6: Go, go, go, go, go!
一個大怪物剛從上面下來！
SOLDIER 5: Something big just went off down here!
將軍，你聽聽這個！
General, you should hear this!
浩克在街上！重複，浩克在街上！
The Hulk is in the street!I repeat, the Hulk is in the street!
不可能，你先照顧好自己，年輕人
That's impossible.You get a hold of yourself, young man.
先穩住，你的位置是？
You get it together. What is your position?
121街，往北開向百老匯！
121st Street, heading north on Broadway!
回頭
Turn us around.
回頭了，為什麼要回頭？
We're going back. Why are we going back?
該死！給我圖像！
Damn it! Give me eyes down there!
遵命，長官！
Yes, sir!
那他媽的是什麼？
What the hell was that?
行動，行動！
Go, go, go!
(SIRENS WAlLING)
不！
No!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
你的人？
One of yours?
老天，你都幹了什麼？
Oh, my God. What have you done?
朝他開火，朝他開火！
OFFlCER: Fire at him, fire at him!
你覺得步槍能傷到它？
Do you think a rifle's gonna hurt that?
來吧！
Come on!
爽
Sweet.
(ABOMINATION ROARING)
耶！
Booyah!
(LAUGHING)
(CAR ALARMS BEEPING)
快跑，士兵！
Get out of there, soldier!
斯黛西！!
Stacy!
讓我痛快打一架！
Give me a real fight!
長官？
Sir?
讓他們帶上所有東西，還有頭盔
Tell them to bring everything they've got and head for Harlem.
得我上，你得帶我回去
It has to be me.You have to take me back there.
你說什麼？
What are you saying?
你覺得你能搞定？
You think you can control it?
不，不是搞定，不知道，盡力吧
No, no, not control it,but, I don't know, maybe aim it.
如果失敗了呢？
And what if you can't ?
這是我們造成的局面
We made this thing.
我們所有人
All of us.
拜託了
Please.
- 在附近降落 - 不，這個高度就可以了
-Land us near it. -No, no. No, keep us high.
開後艙門
Open the back door.
布魯斯！布魯斯，別！停下！你幹嘛？
Bruce! Bruce, stop!Stop! What are you doing?
想想看！你都不一定能變身！
Think about this!You don't even know if you'll change!
你沒必要這樣！求你了，別傻了！
You don't have to do this!Please, this is insane!
貝蒂，我得試試
Betty, I've got to try.
對不起
I'm sorry.
該死！
Oh, shit!
- 拉她進來！ - 來吧，小姐
-Get her in here! -Come on, miss.
(HULK GROWLING)
在那裡，貝蒂！
There. Betty!
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
(ROARING)
浩克！
Hulk!
Yeah!
(BOTH GROWLING)
(ABOMINATION LAUGHING)
來吧！
Come on!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
(ROARING)
你就這兩下子？
Is that all you've got?
用那個，士兵！給他點幫助！
Use that thing, soldier! Give him some help!
幫哪個？
Which one?
綠色的那個，白癡！你以為呢？
Help the green one, damn it!Which one do you think?
把另一個做掉！
Cut the other one in half!
羅斯！
Ross!
跟住他！
Keep it on him!
(HULK AND ABOMINATION GRUNTING)
- 我得降落了！ - 挺住！
PlLOT: Look, I got to put it down! GENERAL: Hang on!
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(ABOMINATION AND HULK GRUNTING)
爸爸？
Dad?
(GROANING)
你疼嗎？我來幫你
Are you hurt? Let me help you.
我沒事，找路出去先
I'm all right. Just find a way out.
(GROWLING)
(CHUCKLING)
你不配這種力量！看著她死吧！
You don't deserve this power!Now watch her die!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
小心！
Look out!
將軍？
General?
還有遺言嗎？
Any last words?
浩克斬！
Hulk smash!
(ROARING)
住手！
BETTY: Stop!
(ROARING)
沒事了
It's okay.
貝蒂
Betty.
(GROWLING)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
（電量低）
（貝拉·庫拉，英屬哥倫比亞）
（貝蒂·羅斯，卡爾沃大學）
(HEART BEATING)
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
已經31天沒有事故發生
已經0天沒有事故發生
加滿
GENERAL: Reload.
Reload.
瞧你這垂頭喪氣的樣子
TONY: The smell of stale beer and defeat.
我不喜歡說「早跟你說過」之類的話，將軍
You know, I hate to say,"I told you so," General,
但那個超級士兵計劃 不是無緣無故被凍結的
but that Super Soldier programme was put on ice for a reason.
我一直覺得硬件更加可靠一些
I've always felt hardware was more reliable.
- 斯塔克  - 將軍
-Stark. -General.
你總是穿得這麼整齊
You always wear such nice suits.
說的沒錯
Touche.
- 聽說你有點麻煩？  - 請指教
-I hear you have an unusual problem. -You should talk.
聽好了
You should listen.
不如我們組織一支隊伍？
What if I told you we were putting a team together?
「我們」？
Who's " we" ?